[{"answer": "Thank you, Piers: Good to be here.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "Well, once they fire you, Piers.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "So, an honest debate, you feel you've been muzzled?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "I think it was being ridiculous.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "How would you honestly have felt?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "No, I'm saying they would be ridiculous to try to draw such an analogy, because remember, there is a reality after 9/11.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "So, are you saying you were ridiculous?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "You still feel uncomfortable.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "And you know what, Piers?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "What do you do when you get on a plane and you see the Muslim in a Muslim garb?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "It's right there.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "What was the honest debate you hoped to have by saying you feel uncomfortable around Muslims on planes?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "No, absolutely not.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Isn't that what you were doing?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "No, and here's the thing.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "You're not putting them in a box?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "You have no regrets, seriously?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "You didn't.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "I would have, that's the thing, you know?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Doesn't it?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "It would have seen it as a form of racial stereotyping.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "No, and I'll tell you what?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "I would agree with him.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "If it was, what is he doing as the standard bearer for the Tea Party now?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know they have a point because they haven't proven it.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Do they have a point?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "I wrote just such a column, just such a column for foxnews.com.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "-- against -- as he calls President Obama -- an African- American?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "We'll talk.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Are you as proud today as you were two or three years ago?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think there's no question we're not solving our problems, that we are not taking action, that we are stuck, we are paralyzed politically.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Well, I'll tell you two things.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "I mean, as a black American, what did you feel the day that you had your first -- not you -- America had its first black president?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "Emotional for you personally?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "I think the whole situation's been disappointing.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Has he been disappointing?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "ILLIAMS: Well, I think personally he's been trying.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Has he personally do you think?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Mitt Romney.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "Who is the Republican who right now do you think would have the best chance of beating Barack Obama?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "\"Could\" is a very strong word.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Do you think he could beat him?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "WILLIAMS: This is the Arthur Laffer piece?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "But no, and it resonates with the American public that's absolutely fed up with the idea of so many loopholes, deductions, tax credits and the like, and the idea that G.E. and others, these large corporations pay no taxes while you and I are looking at the bill and screaming bloody murder.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "The simplify indication of the code as a starting point for the debate is not a bad place to have, is it?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "Well, I think the first thing that pops into my mind is I'm happy but I want more.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "When you look back over this extraordinary run you've had, what do you think of your career?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Is that the secret, to always stay hungry, do you think?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "You yourself have survived ovarian cancer, didn't you?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "It's been eight years, so I would have been 55.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "How old were you, if you don't mind me asking?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "I just began to shake just nonstop all afternoon.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "I mean, that is the moment everybody dreads, isn't it, just right there?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "If you had your time again, would you go public, do you think?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Well, I lost my hearing a little bit.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "What impact did it have on your life, the whole experience?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "Yeah, from chemo.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Permanently?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "Oh yes.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "You can hear me perfectly well, right?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "You wear aids on the set then, as well as microphones and stuff?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Are you completely clear of the cancer?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "It sounds corny to say -- and it took me awhile because right after it, I went through a depression, which I'm hearing now is more and more common.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "How did it change your outlook on life?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Like I wish I had another cosmopolitan.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "When you watch it back now, how do you feel?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "It took a couple to get in the tub.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "How many did it take?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "I'm glad I did it now.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "But to see a script where it says right, at this point, Kathy, you're going to get naked and get into a hot tub, what is your first thought when you see that?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm sure.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Were you also being protective of yourself?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "He was very cool.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "What did Jack make of it all?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "No, I must say I'm not.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Are you friendly with Jack Nicholson?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Yeah, he hasn't done a TV interview in about 50 years apparently.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Is he really?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "He's an enigma really.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "What's he like to be around, to work with?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "ATES: It was.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Because it was such a huge hit?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "I think I closed my eyes and thought, here we go.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "What are you feeling in that second?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Did you really?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I have to kind of go back and say that I -- I grew up in Memphis, Tennessee.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "What do you make of what's going on now in Washington, President Obama, the whole political shakeup at the moment?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "Well, I think he has got to indict these guys from Wall Street.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "Who do you mean by the rat bastards?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "I think it was the catalyst for many.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "ORGAN: Because you believe that basically that was the catalyst for all the problems that are going on now?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 654, "question": "Do you feel alarmed by what you see?", "qSentId": 653}, {"answer": "I don't espouse their views.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "When you see the Tea Party candidates ant the views that they espouse, what do you think?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "I think he's that in him.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "You think Obama has it in him?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "It's like in my hoe, we have a guy in \"Harry's Law,\" Tommy Jefferson.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "But don't you think, playing Devil's advocate, when you watch back \"Primary Colors,\" it has always been ruthless?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "I was married to two pricks, but one thing they can't do is lie convincingly.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "Dying to know what made you say yes?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "It's a great part, isn't it?", "qSentId": 700}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "111021pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "I think everyone would love to be her, huh?", "qSentId": 706}]